Grigoriy Trukhin

+7 (985) 244-67-95 | grigoriy.trukhin@bk.ru | github.com/grisha

SUMMARY

Motivated Analytic and Python developer with 1+ years' experience and have successfully completed 4 Telegram Bots, ordered in Freelance. I am getting a master's degree in applied mathematics. Looking to expand my skills and deepen my knowledge in Data Science.

EXPERIENCE

Data Analyst Feb 2021 – Dec 2022

Zoty (E-commerce)

Moscow, Russia

- Developing code to aggregate sales data from 1C system, .csv files using Python, pandas
- Made dashboards about sales and profits using Tableau
- Reduced advertising costs based on partners positions

Telegram Bot's Developer

Mar 2021 – Nov 2021

Moscow, Russia

- Freelance, 4 projects
 Automated online shop using API of Qiwi, Google Sheets
 - Approving access to online-courses bot
 - Customer information gathering bot that automatically surveys and fills in a .docx file.
 - Bot for matching clients with executors using aiogram, Python, SQL

Projects

Binary classification | Python, scikit-learn, ML, pandas, Jupiter Notebook

Nov 2022 - Nov 2021

- Made exploratory data analysis, using pandas, scikit-learn in Google Colab
- Developed two ML models to different features
- Made an evaluation of a model's accuracy
- GitHub (link)

TG-bot for check-in for the event | Python, Git, WinSCP, Telegram API

Jun 2022 – Jul 2022

- Presented the bot at the "School 21" hackathon, the bot was in the list of finalists
- Managed versions control and push updates, using WinSCP and Git for team of 5 people
- Developed an administrator menu to create and emend information about events. Aggregation of check-in statistics

Courses

- Data analysis using Python (IBM)
- Olympiad Programming (St. Petersburg State University)
- Mathematics and Python for Data analysis (MIPT and Yandex)
- Fundamentals of Statistics (Bioinformatics Institute)
- Deep Learning School (MIPT)
- Interactive SQL Simulator (FEFU)

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages: Python, SQL (Postgres, SQLite), Linux, HTML

Frameworks: aiogram

Developer Tools: Git, PostgreSQL, WinSCP, Tableu, PyCharm, **Libraries**: pandas, scikit-learn, seaborn, NumPy, Matplotlib

EDUCATION

RTU MIREA

Moscow, Russia

Magistracy in Applied Mathematics

Sep. 2022 – present Moscow, Russia

RTU MIREA

Moscow, Russia

Bachalor of science in Industrial Electronics

Sep. 2018 - Aug 2022